Women's Bookstore collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publications, 1969 - 1997; F-111-8; 2.3 m of textual records 212 newspapers
  - The Other Woman, 1972 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67 (Newspaper box 111-34)
    - The Other Woman, vol. 4 no. 3, May 1976 - June 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67-16
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item227.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 4 no. 5, September 1976 - October 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67-17
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item228.
  - Pandora, 1971 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-68 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The Pedestal, 1969 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-69
  - Periodicals - Special Women's Issues, 1971 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-70 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Plexus, 1975 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-71 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - PM The Women's Movement, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-72 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Powerhouse, 1978 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-73 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Power of Women, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-74 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Prairie Fire, 1970 - 1971; F-111-8-0-0-75 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Prime Time, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-76 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Priorities: A Publication of the N.D.P. Women's Committee, 1975 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-77 (Urc tote box 111-23)
    National Democratic Party (NDP); Textual records
  - Priorities: A Publication of the N.D.P. Women's Committee, 1973 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-78 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - The Radical Reviewer, 1980 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-79 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Radical Therapy, 1973 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-80 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Ramparts, 1971 - 1973; F-111-8-0-0-81 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - RAT, 1970; F-111-8-0-0-82 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Science for the People, 1970; F-111-8-0-0-83 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - The Second Wave, 1976 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-84 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Shrew, 1972 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-85 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Siren: Newsletter of Anarcho Feminism, 1973; F-111-8-0-0-86 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Sister, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-87 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Sister Courage, 1975 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-88 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Source, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-89 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Les Sourcières, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-90 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Spare Rib, 1977 - 1979; F-111-8-0-0-91 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Spectre, 1971 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-92 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1970 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-93 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Status of Women News, 1974 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-94 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Le Temps Fou, 1980; F-111-8-0-0-95 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Themis, 1981; F-111-8-0-0-96 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - This Magazine, 1975 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-97 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Transformation, 1971; F-111-8-0-0-98 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Tribad, 1977 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-99 (Urc tote box 111-24)
  - Up From Under, 1970; F-111-8-0-0-100 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Upstream, 1978 - 1985; F-111-8-0-0-101 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Velvet Fist, 1971 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-102 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - VGCC News [Vancouver Gay Community Centre], 1980 - 1983; F-111-8-0-0-103 (Urc tote box 111-25)
    Vancouver Gay Community Centre; Textual records
  - Voices, 1981; F-111-8-0-0-104 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Waves, 1978 - 1979; F-111-8-0-0-105 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Western Canadian Women's News, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-106 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Western Canadian Women's News, 1975 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-107 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Western Voice, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-108 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Wicca, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-109 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - WIN, 1977 - 1979; F-111-8-0-0-110 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Winnipeg Women's Liberation Newsletter, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-111 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Women and Revolution, 1974 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-112 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Women in Struggle, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-113 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - The Women's Page, 1970 - 1971; F-111-8-0-0-114 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Women's Press, 1970 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-115 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter, 1971 - 1978; F-111-8-0-0-116 (Urc tote box 111-25)
  - Yellow Journal, 1970; F-111-8-0-0-117 (Urc tote box 111-25)
- "Rereading Room: The Vancouver Women's Bookstore (1973-1996)" Belkin Gallery art installation, 2018; F-111-9; 1 sound recording; Morris and Helen Belkin Art Gallery
  Series consists of an audio recording of a January 10, 2018 panel discussion with nine former volunteers with the Vancouver Women's Bookstore. The panel was moderated by Alexandra Bischoff and Vincent Tao. It formed part of a reunion celebration held at the Morris and Helen Belkin Gallery on the evening before the opening of the exhibition Beginning with the Seventies: Glut, which exhibited Bischoff's "Rereading Room," a reconstruction of the Vancouver Women's Bookstore.
  Records in electronic form (born-digital)
  Sound recording contained on one wav file. Wave file also available in .mp3 format.
  - Vancouver Women's Bookstore reunion audio recording, January 10, 2018; F-111-9-0-0-0-1; 1 sound recording
    The following text quoted from Alexandra Bischoff's digital records transfer form dated August 20, 2018:
    This audio record was created on January 10, 2018 at the Morris and Helen Belkin Art Gallery - the day preceding the opening of the exhibition "Beginning with the Seventies: GLUT" (January 12 - April 8, 2018). For this exhibition, artist Alexandra Bischoff restaged the Vancouver Women's Bookstore as "Rereading Room," an interactive installation which includes a selection of the Bookstore's inaugural inventory. With the support of the Belkin Art Gallery, Bischoff held a reunion celebration with nine of the Bookstore's volunteers; this recording is from the reunion event.
    Interviewed participants include volunteers that were involved in the organization throughout three decades of its existence, and represent a range of feminist concerns and perspectives. Many, in fact, met for the first time on this occasion. The opinions expressed within the interview are the participants own and do not necessarily reflect the policy of each individual involved, the Vancouver Women's Bookstore at large, or the Belkin Art Gallery.
    Moderating the discussion with Bischoff is Vincent Tao, Librarian of Vancouver artist run centre 221A and Bischoff's collaborator and adviser for Rereading Room's first installation in 2016-17.
    Bischoff, Alexandra; Tao, Vincent; Randall, Nora D.; Daskal, Ann; Azrael, Miriam Delanye; Bell, Carolyn; Shefrin, Elizabeth; Mitchell, Jeannine; L'Estrange, Sarah; Hudson, Kathleen; Ali, Karen Benbassat; Records in electronic form (born-digital)